HEY!
HEY.
LISTEN, YOU GUYS THINK
I HAVE A CHANCE
WITH JANINE?
OH, HONEY, WE HAVE
BEEN THROUGH THIS BEFORE.
YEAH. DON'T DO
THIS TO YOURSELF.
SHE MADE IT PRETTY CLEAR
IT IS NOT GOING TO HAPPEN.
WELL, ALL RIGHT, THEN.
I GUESS I SHOULDN'T
GET TOO EXCITED ABOUT THE FACT
THAT I JUST KISSED HER!
ARE YOU SERIOUS?!
REALLY?
YEAH? WELL, WE'LL SEE.
YOU KISSED HER?
OH, WE KISSED IT UP REAL NICE.
SO YOU
KISSED HER.
SO WHAT HAPPENED AFTER THAT?
I CAME OVER HERE
TO TELL YOU GUYS.
SO SHE'S JUST WAITING
OVER THERE FOR YOU?
YEAH.
♪ SO NO ONE TOLD YOU
LIFE WAS GONNA BE THIS WAY ♪
♪ YOUR JOB'S A JOKE,
YOU'RE BROKE ♪
♪ YOUR LOVE LIFE'S D.O.A. ♪
♪ IT'S LIKE YOU'RE ALWAYS
STUCK IN SECOND GEAR ♪
♪ WHEN IT HASN'T BEEN
YOUR DAY, YOUR WEEK ♪
♪ YOUR MONTH,
OR EVEN YOUR YEAR ♪
♪ BUT I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU'RE THERE
FOR ME, TOO. ♪
I GOT TO GO.
OKAY.
I'M GOING TO BE
REALLY LATE FOR DANCE CLASS.
OKAY.
OKAY, NOW
I'M REALLY LEAVING.
OKAY. ALL RIGHT.
OKAY.
BUT, HEY, CAN YOU JUST...
JUST LEAVE YOUR LIPS?
BYE.
HAVE YOU KISSED HER YET?
IT'S AWESOME.
YOU KNOW, I COULD DO IT FOREVER.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
SHE KISSES BETTER
THAN MY MOM COOKS.
I AM SO GLAD YOU
SAID "COOKS."
OH, HEY, RACHEL, SWEETHEART
YOU HAVE GOT TO TELL
THE POST OFFICE THAT
YOU HAVE MOVED, OKAY?
WE'RE STILL GETTING
ALL YOUR BILLS AND STUFF.
OH.
OOH, OOH, POTTERY BARN.
YOU CAN THROW
THE REST AWAY.
I'M NOT YOUR GARBAGE MAN.
I'M YOUR MAILMAN.
MONICA, LOOK.
LOOK, LOOK, LOOK.
HERE IS THAT TABLE
THAT I ORDERED.
AH...
YOU GOT IT FROM
POTTERY BARN?
YEAH.
IT'S AN APOTHECARY
TABLE.
DOES ANYONE EVEN KNOW
WHAT AN APOTHECARY IS?
A PHARMACIST.
( imitating mockingly ):
"A PHARMACIST."
RACH, PHOEBE HATES
POTTERY BARN.
I HATE POTTERY BARN, TOO.
THEY KICKED ME OUT OF THERE
JUST BECAUSE I SAT ON A BED.
YOU TOOK OFF YOUR PANTS
AND CLIMBED UNDER THE SHEETS.
I WAS TIRED.
PHOEBE HATES
POTTERY BARN?
YEAH, SHE HATES ALL
MASS-PRODUCED STUFF.
SHE THINKS HER FURNITURE
SHOULD HAVE A HISTORY--
A STORY BEHIND IT.
THIS HAS
THEY HAD TO SHIP IT
ALL THE WAY FROM
THE WHITE PLAINS STORE.
IT'S GOT TO BE
ONE OF A KIND.
YOU KNOW, LIKE
THE, UM....
WHAT'S THAT GOD-AWFUL
CERAMIC FRUIT BOWL
THAT SHE HAS ON
HER COUNTER?
HEY, I MADE THAT FOR HER.
YOU MADE POTTERY?
YEAH. I MADE IT
OUT OF THIS FRUIT BOWL
I FOUND IN THE GARBAGE.
I'M TELLING YOU
IF YOU PUT THAT
IN HER APARTMENT
YOU WILL NEVER
HEAR THE END OF IT.
OKAY, FINE, I'LL
JUST TELL HER
THAT IT'S AN ANTIQUE
APOTHECARY TABLE.
SHE DOESN'T HAVE TO KNOW
WHERE IT CAME FROM.
OH, I LOVE
THESE LITTLE DRAWERS.
OH, LOOK, LOOK, IT SAYS
THAT IT HOLDS 300 CDs.
AH, JUST LIKE
THE APOTHECARY TABLES OF YORE.
SO THEN THE
FARMER SAYS
"THAT'S NOT A COW AND
YOU'RE NOT MILKING."
I AM SO GLAD
THAT YOU GUYS GOT TOGETHER.
CHANDLER AND I
ARE ALWAYS LOOKING
FOR A COUPLE TO GO OUT WITH,
AND NOW WE HAVE ONE.
LOOK AT US-- WE'RE
A COUPLE OF COUPLES.
I HAD SO MUCH
FUN TONIGHT.
AND WHAT A
GREAT RESTAURANT.
YEAH, YEAH, AND CHANDLER
I CAN'T BELIEVE I LET YOU
PAY FOR THIS ONE.
THANKS AGAIN, MAN.
SO IF YOU GUYS WANT
TO COME OVER TOMORROW
I'LL MAKE THAT PASTA THING
I WAS TELLING YOU ABOUT.
OH, THAT WOULD
BE GREAT.
BUT, HEY, LOOK
AT LEAST LET US
BRING THE WINE.
JOEY, YOU DON'T HAVE TO.
I INSIST.
YOU'LL GET
THE WINE, RIGHT?
YEAH, OKAY.
OKAY, GOOD
NIGHT, GUYS.
SEE YOU
TOMORROW.
CAN'T WAIT.
HOW ARE WE GOING
TO GET OUT OF THAT ONE?
WHAT?
I CAN'T HANDLE
TWO NIGHTS IN A ROW WITH THEM.
WHAT'S WRONG WITH
MONICA AND CHANDLER?
I DON'T KNOW,
THEY'RE JUST A LITTLE... BLAH.
"BLAH"?
WELL, YOU KNOW, HE'S BLAH.
SHE'S JUST...
SHE'S VERY LOUD
FOR SUCH A SMALL PERSON.
UH, THEY'RE, LIKE,
MY BEST FRIENDS.
ARE YOU SAYING WE CAN'T
HANG OUT WITH THEM
'CAUSE THAT WOULD BE
KIND OF A PROBLEM.
OF COURSE WE CAN STILL
HANG OUT WITH THEM.
JUST, YOU KNOW, NOT TWO
NIGHTS IN A ROW.
OKAY?
I GUESS.
THANK YOU.
HMM.
IF YOU WANT,
I'LL SELL MY FRIENDS
AND USE THE MONEY
TO BUY YOU PRESENTS.
HEY.
OOH, WHAT A GREAT TABLE.
WHERE? WHERE DID YOU GET IT?
GUESS.
UM, A FLEA MARKET.
OH!
SEE, I KNEW. I KNEW YOU WOULD
GET IT ON THE FIRST GUESS.
ISN'T IT COOL?
IT'S AN APOTHECARY
TABLE.
WOW...
OH, YOU CAN JUST IMAGINE THAT
THIS IS WHERE THEY KEPT ALL
THE STUFF TO MAKE
THEIR POTIONS, YOU KNOW.
YES.
YOU CAN ALMOST
SMELL THE OPIUM.
ALMOST.
OH, HOW MUCH WAS IT?
ONLY 500 BUCKS.
500 BUCKS AT A FLEA MARKET?
OH, OKAY, SEE,
I THOUGHT YOU MEANT
HOW MUCH WAS IT
WHEN IT WAS NEW
YOU KNOW,
LIKE BACK THEN?
OH, NO.
I MEAN, IT WAS
AT A FLEA MARKET
SO IT WAS, YOU KNOW,
IT WAS, LIKE, A DOLLAR.
A DOLLAR?
AND 50.
SO, YOU KNOW, IT WAS,
LIKE, ONE AND 50 DOLLARS.
OH, OKAY, THEY GAVE YOU
THE OLD-TIME PRICING.
YEAH.
WELL, WHAT PERIOD
IS IT FROM?
UH, IT'S FROM YORE.
LIKE THE DAYS OF YORE, YOU KNOW.
YES, YES, I DO.
GOD... OH, IT'S
JUST PERFECT.
WOW, I BET IT HAS
A GREAT STORY
BEHIND IT, TOO.
DID THEY TELL YOU ANYTHING?
LIKE, YOU KNOW,
WHERE IT'S FROM OR...?
OH, YES, THAT I KNOW.
THIS IS FROM, UH,
WHITE PLAINS.
( gasps )
MM-HMM.
OH, IT SOUNDS LIKE
SUCH A MAGICAL PLACE.
HEY! I'M HERE.
HEY.
OH... OH, MY GOD.
YOU LIKE IT?
OH, MY GOD.
IT'S MY NEW
APOTHECARY TABLE.
ROSS, PHOEBE IS GOING
TO BE HERE ANY SECOND.
SHE CANNOT SEE THIS.
WELL, WHY NOT?
SHE'LL LOVE IT.
IT'S THE REAL THING.
I GOT IT AT POTTERY BARN.
I KNOW YOU DID.
I BOUGHT THE SAME ONE.
AND IF SHE SEES YOUR TABLE,
SHE'S GOING TO KNOW
THAT I LIED TO HER.
I TOLD HER THAT OURS
WAS AN ORIGINAL.
WHY DID YOU DO THAT?
BECAUSE SHE HATES POTTERY BARN.
SHE HATES POTTERY BARN?
I KNOW, I KNOW.
SHE SAYS IT'S ALL MASS-PRODUCED;
NOTHING IS AUTHENTIC
AND EVERYONE WINDS UP
HAVING THE SAME STUFF.
SO, COME ON. SHE'S GOING
TO BE HERE ANY SECOND.
CAN WE PLEASE JUST
COVER THIS UP
WITH SOMETHING, PLEASE.
NO, NO. I AM NOT
GOING TO HIDE IT FROM PHOEBE.
OH, ALTHOUGH I DID GET SOME
GREAT POTTERY BARN SHEETS.
OOH!
OH, I FORGOT THEY MADE SHEETS.
YAH.
I STILL CAN'T BELIEVE
SHE HATES POTTERY BARN.
ROSS, GET OVER IT.
IT'S NOT LIKE SHE HATES YOU.
YEAH, BUT POTTERY BARN.
YOU KNOW WHAT I THINK?
SHE'S WEIRD, YOU KNOW.
IT'S BECAUSE SHE'S A TWIN.
TWINS ARE WEIRD.
ROSS, SHE'S NOT WEIRD.
SHE JUST LIKES HER STUFF
TO BE ONE OF A KIND.
YOU KNOW WHAT'S NOT
ONE OF A KIND?
A TWIN.
HEY.
OH, PHOEBE'S HERE.
SO LET'S TURN OUT
ALL THE LIGHTS
AND WE'LL JUST
WATCH THE MOVIE.
OKAY. HEY, OOH,
COOL SHEET.
OH, YOU LIKE IT?
YOU WANT TO KNOW
WHERE I GOT IT?
SURE.
HE GOT IT AT A FLEA MARKET.
YOU BOUGHT YOUR SHEETS
AT A FLEA MARKET?
ROSS, YOU'VE GOT TO LOOSEN
THE PURSE STRINGS A LITTLE.
HEY.
DINNER WILL BE READY
IN 20 MINUTES.
I'M SO EXCITED.
HERE IS THE BOTTLE
OF WINE FOR YOU
TO BRING
OVER TONIGHT.
YOU WERE GOING TO BUY
MONICA FLOWERS
BUT YOU COULDN'T
AFFORD IT
BECAUSE YOU PAID FOR
DINNER LAST NIGHT.
THANKS, THANKS.
BUT, UH, ACTUALLY, IT'S
JUST GOING TO BE ME TONIGHT.
WHAT HAPPENED
TO JANINE?
WELL, SHE'S, UH,
REALLY SICK.
OH, THAT'S TOO BAD.
YEAH, SHE'S BEEN
IN THERE ALL DAY.
HIGH FEVER, NOSE PROBLEM...
IT'S... PHLEGM, PHLEGM,
PHLEGM, PHLEGM, PHLEGM.
( door opening )
MONICA, CHANDLER.
I'M REALLY, REALLY
SORRY ABOUT TONIGHT.
I DON'T KNOW
IF JOEY TOLD YOU
BUT I JUST COULDN'T
GET OUT OF GOING
TO THIS PLAY.
I'M SORRY.
HAVE A GREAT TIME, HUH?
BYE.
THAT'S FUNNY.
I SAW NO PHLEGM.
NO, NO,
SHE REALLY IS SICK.
THEN WHY IS SHE
GOING TO A PLAY?
UH, WELL, YOU KNOW--
STARVE A FEVER,
GO TO A PLAY FOR A COLD.
JOEY, WHY IS JANINE NOT
COMING OVER FOR DINNER?
WELL, UH
SHE DIDN'T WANT TO HANG OUT
WITH YOU GUYS
TWO NIGHTS IN A ROW.
I'M SO SORRY.
WHY DOES SHE NOT WANT
TO HANG OUT WITH US?
BECAUSE SHE, UH, SHE...
SHE THINKS THAT YOU ARE BLAH
AND-AND THAT YOU
MONICA, ARE TOO LOUD.
( loudly ):
WHAT?!
( hushed ):
WHAT?
SO SHE WAS JUST PRETENDING
TO HAVE A GOOD TIME
LAST NIGHT?
SHE WAS LYING
TO OUR FACES?
Monica:
I CAN'T
BELIEVE THIS.
I MEAN, WHO IS
SHE TO JUDGE US?
WE COULD NOT HAVE
BEEN NICER TO HER.
AND I AM NOT BLAH.
I AM A HOOT.
I KNOW, I KNOW.
YOU GUYS,
DON'T BE MAD.
I'M SURE SHE JUST SAID
THAT STUFF
BECAUSE SHE WAS
NERVOUS 'CAUSE
YOU GUYS ARE,
LIKE, MY BEST FRIENDS.
YOU KNOW,
AND IT WAS OUR FIRST DATE
PLUS, SHE'S REALLY SICK.
NO, NO, YOU SAID
YOU MADE THAT UP.
I KNOW, BUT DON'T YOU THINK
THE SICK THING
IS WAY BETTER
THAN THE PLAY THING?
WELL, THEY'RE BOTH GOOD.
I GENERALLY JUST GO
WITH MONICA'S DRUNK AGAIN.
COME ON, YOU GUYS,
COME ON, PLEASE, PLEASE
JUST GIVE HER
ANOTHER CHANCE, HUH?
SHE'LL COME AROUND,
I PROMISE.
OF COURSE WE WILL.
COME ON, WE'VE
GOT TO MAKE DINNER.
OKAY.
Monica:
I DO NOT LIKE THAT WOMAN!
I CAN HEAR YOU!
Monica:
I AM LOUD.
( together)
AW.
( all laughing )
HEY, PHEEBS, CAN YOU PLEASE
NOT PUT YOUR FEET UP
ON MY NEW...
OLD SHEET?
OH, SURE.
OH!
AAH!
MY APOTHECARY TABLE!
WHAT?!
NO!
ROSS, WHERE
DID YOU GET THIS?!
I GOT IT
AT POTTERY BARN, OKAY?!
OH, MY GOD!
PHOEBE, POTTERY BARN
HAS RIPPED OFF
THE DESIGN OF OUR ANTIQUE!
( gasping ):
WOW! OH, MY GOD!
WELL, IF THEY'VE RIPPED
OFF OUR TABLE
OURS MUST BE WORTH
MUCH MORE THAN ONE
AND 50 DOLLARS.
WOW, THIS DOESN'T
EVEN SMELL LIKE OPIUM.
OF COURSE NOT,
IT SMELLS LIKE WINE
WHICH YOU SPILLED.
AND THANKS FOR WRECKING
MY SHEET, BY THE WAY.
OH, ROSS, CALM DOWN.
I'LL GIVE YOU
THE 80 CENTS.
OKAY, ONE MORE TIME.
CHANDLER, WOULD YOU LIKE
SOME MORE ORANGE JUICE?
PERFECT DECIBEL.
I KNOW!
HEY.
SO, UH, WHAT ARE YOU GUYS DOING?
OH, NOTHING.
WE'RE JUST TALKING.
YOU KNOW,
BLAH, BLAH, BLAH.
LOOK, COME ON, YOU GUYS.
YOU SAID
YOU WERE GOING TO TRY.
ALL RIGHT, LOOK,
I CAME OVER HERE
TO INVITE YOU GUYS TO A MOVIE
WITH ME AND JANINE.
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
WELL, I'D LIKE TO,
BUT I'M...( whispering )
HA, HA, VERY FUNNY....
LOOK, I DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO DO.
I REALLY WANT YOU GUYS
TO GET ALONG.
JUST, PLEASE,
COME TO THE MOVIE WITH US.
YOU OWE ME.
WE OWE YOU?
THAT'S RIGHT.
I HELPED YOU GUYS
OUT A LOT
IN THE START
OF YOUR RELATIONSHIP.
I HELPED YOU SNEAK AROUND
FOR, LIKE, SIX MONTHS.
I LOOKED LIKE AN IDIOT...
AND-AND I WAS HUMILIATED.
AND I ONLY MADE $200.
WE DIDN'T GIVE YOU
ANY MONEY.
YOU DON'T THINK I KNOW THAT?!
I CAN'T DECIDE WHETHER
IT WOULD GO BETTER
NEXT TO THE NEW
WICKER DINING CHAIR
THE SAHARA DESK
OR THE PARKER
CONSOLE TABLE.
WOW, I DIDN'T KNOW
THERE WAS A POTTERY BARN
UP HERE.
I KNOW, I KNOW,
I WENT A LITTLE CRAZY.
A LITTLE?
YOUR PLACE LOOKS LIKE PAGE 72
OF THE CATALOG.
OH, LOOK AT THAT.
THE ORNAMENTAL BIRD CAGE, LARGE.
HEY.
ROSS, BE CAREFUL.
THAT IS VERY OLD.
OKAY, EARLY COLONIAL
BIRD MERCHANTS
USED TO BRING THEIR BIRDS
TO MARKET IN THAT.
FASCINATING.
( Phoebe gasping )
ANOTHER AMAZING FIND.
WOW!
OH, I BET THIS HAS
A GREAT STORY, TOO.
IT DOES, IT DOES.
IT IS A ROOM-SEPARATING
APPARATUS FROM COLONIAL TIME.
AH.
HUH, A LOT OF
THIS STUFF
IS FROM THE
COLONIAL TIMES.
HEY, WHAT ARE SOME OTHER
TIME PERIODS, RACHEL?
WELL, THERE'S YORE...
( clears throat ):
AND, UH...
YOU KNOW, YESTERYEAR.
YEAH... NO, I'M TELLING YOU
RACHEL HAS SUCH A GOOD EYE
FOR THIS STUFF.
ROSS, YOU KNOW,
IF YOU EVER DECIDE
TO REDECORATE--
AND I THINK THAT YOU SHOULD--
YOU SHOULD ASK RACHEL TO HELP.
OH, HONEY,
HE DOESN'T NEED MY HELP.
COME ON. I THINK HE'S READY
TO GET RID OF THE...
WHAT DID YOU CALL IT?
THE "CHEAP KNOCKOFFS"
AND "DINOSAUR JUNK."
REALLY?
HEY, YOU KNOW WHAT?
SINCE YOU HAVE
SUCH A GREAT SENSE
OF WHAT I NEED,
UH, OH, HERE'S 60 BUCKS.
WHY DON'T YOU
TAKE PHOEBE
DOWN TO THAT COLONIAL
FLEA MARKET OF YOURS
AND GET ME SOME STUFF.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I DON'T REALLY THINK
PHOEBE WANTS TO COME...
NO, I DO WANT TO.
OH, SHE DOES WANT TO.
SHE DOES WANT TO.
PHEEBS, I DON'T
KNOW WHAT TO SAY.
I GUESS THE
FLEA MARKET
WAS JUST
BETTER LAST TIME.
AT LEAST I GOT
THESE SHEETS FOR ROSS.
YEAH.
UGH. LOOK AT THIS,
POTTERY BARN.
YEAH, YOU KNOW WHAT?
DON'T LOOK AT IT.
SERIOUSLY,
LOOK, LOOK!
THERE'S THE COFFEE TABLE
THEY STOLE FROM US.
AAH, THOSE BASTARDS!
LET'S GO.
HEY, THAT FAN
KIND OF LOOKS LIKE OURS
AND THE BIRD CAGE AND...
WAIT A SEC, THIS IS
OUR EXACT LIVING ROOM.
NO, NO, NO, IT'S NOT.
NO, IT'S NOT.
COME ON, PHOEBE,
OURS IS TOTALLY DIFFERENT.
WE DON'T HAVE THE...
WE DON'T HAVE...
WE DON'T HAVE THAT LAMP.
AND THAT SCREEN IS,
YOU KNOW
ON THE OTHER SIDE.
OH, MY GOD. THIS IS WHERE
YOU GOT ALL OUR STUFF--
POTTERY BARN,
OH, MY GOD!
OKAY, OKAY, WAIT,
I DID, ALL RIGHT,
I'M SORRY...
IT'S JUST THAT, PHOEBE,
I WANTED THIS STUFF
AND I KNOW HOW YOU FEEL
ABOUT POTTERY BARN.
SO JUST... COME ON,
DON'T BE MAD.
BUT I AM MAD,
I AM MAD
BECAUSE THIS STUFF IS EVERYTHING
THAT IS WRONG WITH THE WORLD
AND IT'S ALL SITTING UP
IN MY LIVING ROOM!
AND ALL I CAN THINK
ABOUT IS
HOW I DON'T HAVE
THAT LAMP!
WELL, THEN, HONEY,
BUY THE LAMP.
HEY, WE HAVE THAT
60 BUCKS FROM ROSS.
I CAN'T, I CAN'T!
UNLESS...
WELL, ARE YOU SAYING
THAT YOU WOULD MOVE OUT
IF I DIDN'T BUY THAT LAMP?
WHA...? NO! I'M NOT
GOING TO MOVE OUT.
ARE YOU SAYING
THAT YOU WOULD MOVE OUT
IF I DIDN'T BUY
THAT LAMP?!
OH, YES! I WOULD
SO MOVE OUT.
OKAY, THEN I DON'T
HAVE A CHOICE!
I HAVE TO BUY THAT LAMP!
THAT'S RIGHT.
BUT AT LEAST
THE APOTHECARY TABLE'S REAL.
WELL, THIS WAS GREAT.
DIDN'T EVERYBODY
HAVE A GREAT TIME?
WELL, I DID.
I REALLY DID.
YOU KNOW, GUYS,
I GOT TO SAY
I'M SORRY IF I WAS
A LITTLE WEIRD
AFTER THE LAST TIME
WE WENT OUT.
I GUESS I WAS JUST NERVOUS
OR SOMETHING.
THAT'S TOTALLY
UNDERSTANDABLE.
YEAH, DON'T WORRY
ABOUT IT.
SO WE CAN GO OUT AGAIN?
OH, YEAH.
ABSOLUTELY.
OH, WELL, GOOD NIGHT.
GOOD NIGHT.
SEE, HUH?
WASN'T THAT FUN?
WE HAVE GOT TO MOVE.
WHAT?
I KNEW IT!
YOU KNOW, YOU'RE NOT
SO QUIET YOURSELF, MISSY!
AND I'M BLAH?
LISTEN, THE ONLY THING
THAT'S MORE BORING
THAN WATCHING
MODERN DANCE
IS HAVING TO LISTEN
TO YOU TALK ABOUT IT.
( imitating Janine ):
"OH, CHANDLER, I JUST LOST
MYSELF IN THE MOVEMENT."
YOU KNOW,
I KNOW YOU'RE TALKING
BUT ALL I HEAR IS,
"BLAH, BLAH, BLAH
BLAH, BLAH."
ALL RIGHT, YOU AND ME,
LET'S GO, RIGHT NOW!
ALL RIGHT, ENOUGH, ENOUGH!
ENOUGH, ENOUGH!
YOU TWO GO HOME.
I'VE GOT TO TALK
TO JANINE.
I REALLY THINK
YOU CAN TAKE HER.
YOU BETTER HOPE
I DON'T SEE YOU
IN THE HALLWAY!
ALL RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT, UH...
WE'VE GOT A LITTLE BIT
OF A PROBLEM HERE.
THESE PEOPLE ARE
MY FRIENDS.
YOU CAN'T TREAT
THEM THAT WAY.
THEY SAID STUFF TO ME, TOO,
YOU KNOW.
I KNOW, I KNOW, AND
I'M GOING TO TALK
TO THEM ABOUT IT.
BUT... THEY MEAN
SO MUCH TO ME.
THEY'RE LIKE MY
FAMILY, YOU KNOW.
IF YOU GUYS ARE GOING
TO BE FIGHTING
ALL THE TIME...
I DON'T THINK
WE CAN BE TOGETHER.
IT JUST CAN'T
WORK, OKAY?
IT CAN'T.
I'M VERY UPSET.
OKAY, OKAY, WOULD IT HELP
IF I WENT OVER
AND APOLOGIZED?
YEAH, YEAH, THAT WOULD BE
VERY HELPFUL, YEAH.
WHAT DID I TELL YOU
ABOUT THE HALL?
I WAS JUST COMING OVER HERE
TO APOLOGIZE FOR MY BEHAVIOR.
I WOULD REALLY LIKE IT
IF WE COULD BE FRIENDS.
WELL, I KNOW THAT
WOULD MAKE JOEY HAPPY
SO... I WOULD
LIKE THAT, TOO.
GREAT.
COME ON.
WELL, I'M GLAD WE
WORKED THINGS OUT.
ME, TOO.
OKAY, I'LL SEE YOU.
BYE.
OR I'LL HEAR YOU.
THAT'S IT, BIG GIRL,
COME ON!
WAIT!
YOU BETTER RUN!
DID YOU HEAR THAT?
YEAH.
WHAT AM I GOING TO DO?
I DON'T KNOW, I'M SORRY, MAN.
YOU WANT TO GO WATCH?
YEAH.
HEY. HOW YOU DOING?
DID SHE MOVE OUT?
PRETTY MUCH. YEAH.
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU BROKE UP
WITH HER JUST LIKE THAT.
WELL, WHEN IT'S NOT RIGHT,
YOU KNOW IT.
YOU OKAY?
YEAH, I'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
YOU KNOW WHAT
WOULD CHEER YOU UP?
WHAT?
I'M GIVING THIS LECTURE
ON EROSION THEORIES
TOMORROW NIGHT.
I THINK YOU SHOULD COME.
( laughing )
YOU'RE RIGHT,
THAT DID CHEER ME UP.